https://berrymoorman.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICY
BERRY MOORMAN P.C. PRIVACY POLICY
Berry Moorman P.C. respects the privacy of all individuals who visit our website. This privacy policy describes the information we collect when you visit our website and applications, how that information may be used, and how we protect your information.
Information Collected by Berry Moorman P.C.
Information You Give Us
We only collect and store information, including personally identifiable information, when you specifically provide it to us.  Berry Moorman P.C. will not disclose personally identifiable information provided by you to any third party without your express authorization, unless required by law. Berry Moorman P.C. only uses personally identifiable information provided by you for the sole purposes of responding to your requests and inquiries.
Such information may include:
Your email address
Your name
Your contact information
Automatically Collected Information
We receive and store certain types of non-personally identifiable information, such as information about your use of the website.  Berry Moorman P.C. may collect website-visitation statistical information through cookies, tools such as Google Analytics, and other technology in order to speed your navigation of the website.
Log Files
The website server automatically recognizes the Internet Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) from which you access the website.
How Berry Moorman P.C Uses the Information it Collects
We may use third-party service providers to monitor and analyze your use of our website.  Google Analytics are web analytics services that track and report traffic in order to monitor the use of our website. For Google Analytics, this data is shared with other Google services.
Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.
Security
In order to protect your information and data contained on our website, Berry Moorman P.C. employs standard technical, physical, and administrative security measures. Communications with our website are encrypted through Secured Socket Layer (“SSL”) connections.
Berry Moorman P.C. makes every effort to protect your information.  However:
BERRY MOORMAN P.C. CANNOT GUARANTEE SECURITY.  BERRY MOORMAN P.C. ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT OCCURS BY NEGLIGENCE OF BERRY MOORMAN P.C., ERRORS IN TRANSMISSION, UNAUTHORIZED OR ILLEGAL ACCESS, OR ANY OTHER VEHICLE FOR DISCLOSURE.
External Links
Berry Moorman P.C. is not responsible for any content or policies of other websites that are accessible by hyperlink from our website. This privacy policy only applies to the information and content maintained by Berry Moorman P.C. on our website.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
This privacy policy is subject to change without notice and Berry Moorman P.C. will post the amended terms on this website.
Contact Information
If you have any concerns about your privacy, contact us at info@berrymoorman.com.
HomeFirm Overview
Our History
Practices
Alternative Dispute Resolution Business & Corporate Civil Litigation Estate Planning Estate & Trust Litigation Family Law Immigration International Law Labor & Employment Mergers & Acquisitions Municipal Law & Litigation Nonprofit Real Estate Russia, Ukraine & NIS Tax Trademarks & Copyrights
Attorneys
Donald F. Carney Jr. Sandro DiMercurio Simon M. Edelstein David M. Foy Terrence E. Keating Sheryl A. Laughren Robert W. Morgan Andrea M. Pike George H. Runstadler III John J. Schrot Jr. Mark E. Straetmans Thomas M. Sullivan Patrice M. Ticknor Harvey B. Wallace Randolph M. Wright
News & Publications
Publications Firm News Media
OfficesContact
